前情提要：
Previously on Lost:
我要你从壁炉爬上通风口
I need you to go up through the grate and into the vents.
那个按键必须得按
That button has to be pushed.
好的
OK.
我从你的通风口爬了过去
I crawled through your vents
站在你的电脑前  你知道后来发生什么了?
and I stood at your computer. And you know what happened?
什么都没发生  John
Nothing happened, John.
我根本没输入那些数字
I never entered the numbers.
我也没有按那个按键
I never pressed the button.
如果你想对Libby好点
If you want to do something nice for Libby,
离这三公里外有个美丽的海滩
there's a beautiful beach three kilometers from here.
你可以把她带到那去
You could take her there.
-快  把毯子给我  -毯子?
-Come on, give me the blankets.  -Blankets?
我来搞定毯子 好吧?
I will handle the blankets, OK?
马上带我们去拿枪 就是现在
Take us to the guns. Now.
那个婊子
that bitch.
偷了我的枪  Ana Lucia
She stole my damn gun. Ana Lucia.
她要枪干吗?
Why would she need a gun?
我们抓住了其中一个...其他人
We caught one of them. The Others.
他被关在那
He's locked up in there.
把枪给我  我来杀他
Give me the gun. I'll kill him.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
Michael?
你在造什么?
What are you building?
你好  Ana
Hello, Ana.
你也好啊
hello, yourself.
你可以告诉我了么?
So you gonna tell me?
那是什么?
What is it?
我在建一座教堂
I'm building a church.
你到底为什么要那么做?
why the hell would you wanna do that?
因为有人要我这么做
Because I was told to.
谁?
Told to by who?
我刚刚被要求要这么做 我想是在梦里
I was just told. I think it was in a dream.
像这样的梦?
A dream like this one?
你得去帮助John
You need to help John.
Yemi?
你好  哥哥
Hello, brother.
噢  Yemi  原谅我
Yemi. Forgive me.
我应该听你的  你是对的
I should have listened to you. You were right.
我不是故意要这么做...
I didn't mean to do what I did.
这里正在进行的工作
The work being done in this place
是非常重要的  Eko
is important, Eko.
比任何事情都重要
It is more important than anything
并且这工作正处在危险中
and it is in danger.
你得去帮John
You must help John.
他迷失了他的方向
He has lost his way.
你得叫他带你去问号那
You must make him take you to the question mark.
John是不愿告诉你的
John will not want to show you
你必须逼他说
so you must make him.
Eko...
很多事会让你分心  哥哥
There are many distractions, brother
但你必须克服
but you must move past them.
过去的事就让他过去吧
What is done is done.
-你懂了么?  -是的  Yemi
-Do you understand?  -Yes, Yemi.
还有  Eko...
And, Eko?
带上斧子
Bring the ax.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
你没事吧  伙计?
You all right, mate?
我要去找John
I need to find John.
你在想什么  John?
What were you thinking, John?
-Jack  别说了  -不  Jack  继续说
-Jack Leave him alone.  -No, Jack don't leave him alone.
闭嘴  Sawyer   如果Ana没拿走你的枪...
Shut it, Sawyer. If Ana hadn't lifted your gun...
这样不是很棒吗? 那个拐杖先生
Well, ain't that swell.Gimpy McCrutch over here
为所谓的艺术家Henry Gale打了掩护
covers up that the Artist Formerly Known As Henry Gale
隐瞒了他试图扼死你的女朋友的事
tried to strangle your little amiga
现在她自己要去执行正义,你们却都算到我头上来了
and suddenly it's on me when she goes vigilante.
你还是回到海滩去吧
How about you go back to the beach?
够了 你们俩
Hey enough. Both of you.
Michael  嘿
Michael. Hey.
他开枪打我
He shot me.
-谁? -他溜了 跑掉了
-Who? -He's gone. He ran out.
快  我去追他
-Go. I got him.
我当时正在睡觉然后听到了枪声
I was sleeping and I heard gunshots.
然后我起来跑出了卧室
I got up. I came out of the bedroom
然后...有个家伙
and there was this guy.
他手上拿着枪  并且...
He had a gun and...
好吧 来  我们拉你起来  还好吧?
All right, come on. We gotta get you up, all right?
我来帮你
Let me help you.
她死了
She's dead.
Kate  我们得把她扶起来
Kate, we gotta get her up.
我们把她放到后面的房间去  好么?
We gotta get her up to the back room, OK?
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对： BillSky
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
主啊  赐予我们您的仁慈
Grant us this mercy, O Lord
我们向您祈祷
we beseech thee.
阿门
Amen.
她休克了
She's in shock.
来 我们得用力压这里
All right, we gotta keep pressure on this one.
你能做些什么吗?
Can you do anything?
-Jack  -我听见了
-Jack?  -I heard you.
就这样压住她  好吗?
Just keep pressure on her, OK?
她怎么样了?
How is she?
我在尽我最大的努力
I'm doing what I can.
多久之前?
How long ago?
什么?
What?
这是什么时候发生的?  他什么时候离开的?
When did this happen? How long ago did he leave?
我不知道  呃...
I don't know.
20分钟  可能半个小时之前
Twenty minutes, maybe a half-hour ago.
他向我们三人开枪  一个死了 还有一个...
He shot three people. One of them's dead,one of them...
你去充英雄 谁来照顾Libby呢?
Who's gonna take care of Libby while you're off playing Daniel Boone?
我去
I will go.
John  你有跟踪的经验  对吧?
John, you have tracking experience, yes?
没错
Yeah.
我们一起去找他
We will find his trail together.
你们只要找到任何线索  就马上回来
You find anything,anything, you come right back here
我们再一起想接下来怎么做
and we figure out what we're gonna do next together.
我们走  John
Let's go, John.
离你上次忏悔有多久了?
How long has it been since your last confession?
问得好
Good question.
太久了  我都记不清了
Too many years for me to even remember.
你想让上帝宽恕你什么呢?
What do you wish to ask God's forgiveness for?
你犯了什么罪?
What sins have you committed?
让我想想
let's see.
我和除我妻子以外的女人睡觉
I slept with another woman besides my wife.
一次还是很多次?
Just once or many times?
多少次才算很多次?
How many is "many"?
要接受上帝的宽恕
To receive God's forgiveness
你必须为你的罪行而悔过
you must be penitent for your sins.
我还伪造身份证
I also forged ID papers
给一个想装牧师的家伙
for a guy pretending to be a priest.
你带来了吗?
Do you have it?
你打算怎么做  教士? 扔下你的募捐箱吗?
So what did you do, Padre? Skim from the collection plate?
你知道我在洛杉矶有很多朋友
You know, I've got some friends in Los Angeles.
我能让你和他们联系
I could get you on with them.
为什么?
Doing what?
你知道...某些事
You know, stuff.
早上好  Tunde神父
Good morning, Father Tunde.
早上好  阁下  这是Caldwell先生
Good morning, Monsignor. This is Mr.Caldwell
他在帮我安排去美国的行程
He has been helping me arrange my trip to the United States.
我很抱歉  神父  我有个坏消息
I'm sorry, Father, but I've got some bad news.
你不得不推迟你的行程了
You're gonna have to postpone your trip.
好象有奇迹发生了
It appears we have a miracle.
我的女儿  她...她淹死了
My daughter, she... she drowned.
我很抱歉
I'm very sorry for your loss.
噢  不  你不明白
Oh, no, you don't understand.
她又活过来了
She came back to life.
当时我们在后街那
We were out in the back blocks
Charlotte失足掉进了河里
and Charlotte must have slipped and she went into the river
她不会游泳
and she's not much of a swimmer.
她死了
She was dead
可...第二天她醒了过来
and the next day she woke up.
你还不明白吗?
Don't you understand?
这是奇迹
It's a miracle.
对我们信仰的肯定
A confirmation of faith.
-大家都应该知道 我们需要...  -你女儿现在在哪?
-Everyone needs to know about this.People need  -Where is your daughter now?
在家  和我丈夫在一起
At home  with my husband.
他是怎么想的?
And what does he think?
这应该让全世界都知道
The world needs to know.
我们得告诉罗马教廷   我们得告诉世界...
We need to tell the Vatican. We need to tell the world...
抱歉  我们不能马上这么做   Malkin女士
I'm sorry. We can't just do that, Mrs. Malkin.
教堂需对此事进行深入的调查
The church needs to conduct an investigation
才能公布这件事
before anyone can be told.
Tunde神父会着手去调查的
Father Tunde will start this process
如果你允许的话
if you'll permit him.
Malkin女士  我们失陪一下
Mrs. Malkin, would you excuse us for a moment?
好的
Of course.
阁下  恕我直言
Monsignor, with all due respect
我不能答应你让我做的事
I cannot do what you have asked.
为什么?
Why not?
因为我不相信这个女人说的
Because I do not believe what this woman says.
你觉得我为什么让你去?
Why do you think I chose you?
你是不是发现什么我不知道的了?
Are you seeing something I'm not?
我什么痕迹都没发现
I haven't seen a single track or piece of sign
从我们离开舱口就什么都没发现过
since we left the hatch.
你到底在跟踪什么?
What the hell are you following?
问号在哪?
Where is the question mark?
什么?
what?
问号  John  它在哪?
The question mark, John. Where is it?
你知道吗?
You know what?
你一直在异想天开
You keep chasing after your own shadow.
我要回去了
I'm going back.
我知道你不愿意给我看 但是你必须得这么做
I know you do not want to show me, but you must.
不  我没有义务让你知道任何事
No, I don't have to show you anything.
那对不起了
Then I'm sorry.
你打了我
You hit me.
你为什么...
Why did you?
因为你不太合作
Because you were being difficult.
你疯了么?
Are you insane?
没有
No.
Ana Lucia 你的朋友
Ana Lucia, your friend
刚被杀  而你...
was just murdered and you...
Ana要我来帮助你  John
Ana wants me to help you, John.
帮我什么?
Help me do what?
找到问号
Find the question mark.
你根本不明白自己在说些什么 是吧
You don't even know what you're talking about, do you?
不
No.
但是你知道我在说什么  John
But you know what I am talking about, John
那才是关键
and that is all that matters.
给你
Here.
给你  你不是想找到问号么?
Here. You wanna find your damn question mark?
就这个  在这  就在这里
Here, this is it right here.
给你  拿着吧  这根本什么都不是
Here, take it. Because it's nothing.
凭记忆随便画的  只出现了十秒钟
It's a memory. It's ten seconds of nothing
这是你的舱子  对吧?
This is your hatch, yes?
这不是我的舱子
It's not my hatch.
如果这个天鹅是我们来的地方
If the swan is where we came from
那么我们就往这走
then we go that way.
我们根本就不该来这的
We shouldn't even be out here.
如果我告诉Jack,Henry曾经攻击过Ana Lucia 她也许就不会死了
Ana Lucia would still be alive, if I'd just told Jack that Henry attacked her.
现在她想让我们到这儿来
Now she wants us to go here
她想让我们去这 John 我们一起
She wants us to go here, John. Together.
她在我的梦里告诉我的
She said this in my dream.
噢 对了 在你的梦里
Oh, of course, your dream.
告诉我  John
Tell me, John
你是否曾经跟随你梦的指引?
haven't you ever followed a dream?
那么 罗马教廷会对这很感兴趣 是吗
So, the Vatican's really interested in this one
那要看我怎么写我的报告了
That depends upon what I put in my report.
那么你就从
Why don't you just start by telling me
那天晚上发生了什么开始讲起吧
what happened that night?
我大概在夜里1点接到个电话
Well, I got a call around 1am
Ambrose把这个女孩的尸体送来
Ambos brought this girl in, dead.
她呆在水里已经两个钟头了
She'd been in the water two hours.
你对像这样溺水身亡的事件有经验吗?
Have you had much experience in this type of death?
是的  当然  我从未失误过
Yeah, of course. I'm, I'm an undertaker
呃 我是说 这是我的本职工作
Well, I mean, it's my day job.
我是十分合格的验尸官
I'm perfectly qualified to be a coroner.
我进过医学院
I did go to medical school.
你是什么时候发现她没死?
And when did you find out that she was not dead?
在解剖验尸的时候
During the autopsy.
在解剖验尸的时候?
During the autopsy?
没关系
It's all right.
我没指望你相信我
I didn't expect you to believe me.
我想你个能想要亲自听听
I figured you'd want to have a listen for yourself.
死者为白人女性
Decedent is a Caucasian female.
身高161厘米  体重51.3公斤
161 centimeters, 51.3 kilos.
尸体准备和清洗由可爱的Valerie McDervish清洗完毕
Body was prepped and washed by the very lovely Valerie McDervish.
Ian 别这样
Ian, Stop it.
从标志处开始
Commencing with the post.
这是一起典型的溺水事件
This is a clear case of drowning.
下面开始
I'll begin with
进行胸腔切割
a thoracic...
拿走吧
Take it.
拜托...
No, please.
我再也不想听了
I don't want to ever listen to that tape again.
迷路了?
You lost already?
你的地图不准
Your map is inexact.
你没在开玩笑?
No kidding?
这些地理标志...
These landmarks...
是条河吗?
Is this a river?
不  只是条曲线
No, it's a wavy line.
这不是我画的  是我抄来的
I didn't draw it. I just transcribed it.
我告诉你了  我不知道这是不是地图
I told you I don't even know if it is a map.
假设它是的
Let's assume it is.
那个斧头用来干吗?
What's the ax for?
我现在还不知道
I don't know yet.
飞机是你发现的么?
You were the one that found this plane, yes?
是的
Yeah.
当时它在上面
It was up there.
怎么掉下来的?
And what made it fall?
Boone
Boone使它掉下的
Boone made it fall.
然后他就死了
Then he died.
这个岛需要的牺牲品
A sacrifice that the island demanded.
什么?
Excuse me?
没什么
Nothing.
那么  下一步呢?
So, what's next?
我们露营...
We make camp
休息一下...
get some sleep
等待下一步的指示
and wait for further instruction.
他们到底去哪了?
Where in the hell are they?
冷静点
Just calm down.
在黑夜里追踪不是那么简单的
Finding his trail in the dark is not gonna be easy.
他们马上会回来的
They'll be back.
Jack
她有说什么吗?  Libby?
She say anything? Libby?
她还处于昏迷状态
She's still unconscious.
血止住了
The bleeding's stopped.
那是好消息  是么?
That's good, right?
不
No.
不好
It's not good.
你就没有...
And there's nothing you can?
我能让她更好过点
I can make her comfortable.
但我没有我需要的
But I don't have what I need.
你看着我干吗?
Why look at me?
我两天前就把该死的药都给你了
I gave you all the meds two days ago.
海洛因  Sawyer
The heroin, Sawyer.
等我二十分钟
Give me twenty minutes.
Kate和你一起去
Kate's gonna go with you.
没必要去两人...
It doesn't take two people to carry...
Kate一起去
Kate is going with you.
你在说什么? 干吗要我跟他一起去?
What are you talking about? Why would he need me to go with him?
Jack知道我的海洛因和枪是放在一起的
Jacko here knows his heroin's in my stash with the guns.
所以我要么告诉你东西放在哪
So I can either show you where it's at
要么就让可怜的Libby痛苦下去
or let poor Libby suffer.
是不是这样  医生?
That pretty much it, Doc?
是的  差不多是这样
Yeah. Yeah. That's pretty much it.
我们走吧 雀斑女
Let's go, Freckles
有件事我很好奇
I'm curious about something.
恩  什么事?
Yeah, what's that?
Ana  Lucia怎么拿到你的枪的?
How did Ana Lucia get your gun?
我不知道  肯定是偷的
I don't know. She must have lifted it off me.
她偷了你的枪?
She pickpocketed your gun?
她怎么做到的?
How'd she do that?
我要是知道的话
if I knew how she did it
她就没机会下手了  不是吗?
she wouldn't be able to do it, would she?
你先请
After you.
我以为你是带我去你藏东西的地方
I thought you were taking me to your stash.
别把每件事都想这么复杂?
Do you have to make everything so damn difficult?
进去就好了
Just go in.
你把枪都藏这了
You kept the guns here.
你一直把它们藏在自己底下
All this time, right under you.
骗到你们了吧?
Fooled you, didn't I?
嘿  伙计们
Hey, guys.
你们看到Libby了吗?
You seen Libby around?
Eko
嘘  别把John吵醒了
Shh.You'll wake John.
来
Come.
跟我来.
Follow me.
Yemi
醒醒  John
Wake up, John.
你还好吧  John?
Are you all right, John?
很好
Yeah, yeah.
我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
你做梦了
You had a dream?
有没有梦到一个男的? 一个牧师?
Was there a man? A priest?
你梦到的那个人是我的弟弟
The man that you saw was my brother.
你弟弟
Your brother?
这就是我们要一起来的原因
This is why we needed to come together.
我们会以这种方式得到指示
This is how we are going to be led
-也会通过这种方式知道下一步怎么走  -可我不知道往哪儿走啊
-how we will know where to go next.  -I don't know where to go.
-他有没有告诉你什么? -不  他...
-Did he tell you anything? -No. He...
没有?  什么事都可以?
Nothing? Anything?
梦里的不是我  是你
It wasn't even me. It was you.
那个  那个  没有...
It didn't...
他...
He...
他要我跟着他
he wanted me to follow him.
去哪?
Follow him where?
等在这
Wait here.
Eko  那只是个梦
Eko, it was just a dream.
那很不安全
It's not safe.
Eko
Eko!
神父  恐怕现在不方便说话
Father, I'm afraid it's not a very good time.
你得改日再来
You'll have to come back later.
Malkin女士  我必须和你女儿谈谈
Mrs. Malkin, I must speak to your daughter.
-昨天在教堂  你说...  -我知道我说了什么
-Yesterday in the church you said...  -I know what I said.
现在真的不方便说话
It's just right this minute it's not a very good time.
回房子里去  Joyce
All right. Get back in the house, Joyce.
-把她带进去. -Richard  别这样...
-Get her inside. -Richard, please...
马上进去
Inside. Now.
我知道你来干嘛的  朋友
I know why you're here, friend
不过你大可不必费神
but you can save yourself the trouble.
这里没有发生什么奇迹
What happened here was not a miracle.
给您女儿治疗的医生可不这么认为
The doctor that treated your daughter seems to feel differently.
治疗?
Treated her?
你是说准备把她开膛破肚的家伙
You mean tried to cut her open.
他只是想掩饰自己的疏忽
He's just trying to cover up his own negligence.
他告诉你整个经过了吗?  她是如何"淹死"的
He tell you the whole story --how she supposedly drowned?
她掉进了山里的河中
She fell into a mountain river.
她的身体机能停滞了
Her body shut down.
体温降低使她呈现假死状态
She went into hypothermia, which made her appear dead.
那您的妻子为什么深信这是个奇迹呢?
Then why is your wife so convinced otherwise?
因为她是个狂热的教徒
Cause she's a zealot.
她做的这一切
All of this, everything she's doing
都是为了给我造成困扰
it's to spite me.
她为什么要这样做?
Why would she spite you?
因为她知道我是个骗子
Because she knows I'm a fraud.
因为我的职业是通灵者
Because I make my living as a psychic.
我就是靠这个谋生的
You see, that's what I do.
我收集人们的智慧
I gather intelligence on people
把这些作为己用
and I exploit it.
每天
Every day
我去见那些寻找奇迹的人
I meet people looking for a miracle
但是根本就找不到
desperate to find one.
因为根本没有奇迹可言
But there are none to be had.
至少在这个世界上是没有的
Not in this world, anyway.
我会回去禀告阁下
I will report back to my monsignor
这里没有发生奇迹
that there was no miracle here.
您的女儿活着 这个是最重要的
Your daughter is alive. This is all that matters.
小心
Be careful.
Eko
我没事
I'm fine.
嘿  Eko
Hey, Eko.
上面有什么? 你看到什么了吗?
What's up there? Do you see anything?
不是什么也没有...
I don't see nothing.
这里被撒过盐
It's salted.
什么?
What?
土  掺进了盐所以上面什么也不长
The earth. It's been salted so that nothing can grow.
谁会在这儿撒盐...
Why would anyone wanna salt it?
什么都没有
There's nothing here.
我想他们做了一个圆圈的记号
I believe they made a circle, a target,
做了一个目标 这样从上面就可以看到这个地方
so that this place can be seen from up above.
他们?
They?
什么地方?
What place?
这架飞机掉下来的地方 John  来吧
The place that this plane fell upon, John. Come on.
John
能帮我一把吗?
Will you help me with this?
等等
Wait.
Eko
我来好么?
May I?
好的  请便
Please. Be my guest.
我们本来要开始第一次约会的
We were gonna have our first date.
约会?
Date?
是的 在海滩上来一次野餐
Yeah, Picnic on the beach.
很高兴你没事  伙计
I'm glad you're OK, man.
John
John.
你好  我是Mark Wickmund博士
Hello. I'm Dr. Mark Wickmund,
这是入门指导影片
and this is the orientation film
专为达摩启动计划的第五站所做
for Station 5 of The Dharma Initiative.
第五站  又名珍珠  是一个监视站
Station 5, or The Pearl, is a monitoring station
达摩启动计划中 所有的参与者的一切行动
where the activities of participants in Dharma Initiative projects
都将在此被观察与记录
can be observed and recorded
这不仅为后人留下研究资料
not only for posterity,
同时也为了计划的整体进行
but for the ongoing refinement of the Initiative as a whole.
正如Karen Degroot自己所写
As Karen DeGroot herself has written,
细致的观察
Careful observation
是得到完整真知的唯一途径
is the only key to true and complete awareness.
你们在珍珠监察站内的任务为期三周
Your tour of duty in The Pearl will last three weeks
在此期间  你和你的同伴
and during this time you and your partner
会观测到一个正在进行的心理学实验
will observe a psychological experiment in progress
你们的任务是观察
Your duty is to observe
岛上另一站点的队员
team members in another station on the island.
这些成员
These team members
并不知晓其身处被监视状态
are not aware they are under surveillance
也不知道其身为实验对象
or that they are subjects of an experiment.
你和你的同伴将按八小时制轮流值班
Working in eight-hour shifts,
记录下所观测到的所有情况
you and your partner will record everything you observe
并在我们提供的笔记本上记录下来
in the notebooks we've provided.
这一实验的目的何在? 你们可能对此产生疑问
What is the nature of the experiment, you might ask?
这些实验对象努力完成每项任务
What do these subjects believe they are accomplishing
是为了达成什么目的?
as they struggle to fulfill their tasks?
作为观测者的你们无需了解
You, as the observer, don't need to know.
你们只需记住
All you need to know
这些实验对象
is the subjects
相信其任务的重要性
believe their job is of the utmost importance.
记住  发生的每件事
Remember, everything that occurs,
不管多么小或看起来多么不重要
no matter how minute or seemingly unimportant
都要记录
must be recorded.
一旦一本笔记本记满了
Each time a notebook is filled
你们辛勤观测的结果
with the fruits of your diligent observation,
卷起来 把它放进准备好的容器里
roll it up, and place it in one of the containers provided.
然后只需把该容器
Then simply place the container
放进气动导管里
in the pneumatic tube
然后...嗖的一下
and presto,
我们就能拿到你们的报告了
it will be transported directly to us.
每次八小时轮岗时间到了之后
At the end of your eight-hour shift,
去巴拉渡口
proceed to the Pala Ferry,
你会被带回...
which will take you back to
谨代表  Degroots  Alvar Hanso
On behalf of the DeGroots, Alvar Hanso,
以及全体达摩启动计划成员
and all of us here at The Dharma Initiative
向你们致敬...
Namaste
并祝你们好运
and good luck.
想再看一遍吗?
Would you like to watch that again?
不了
No.
不  我看够了
No, I've seen enough.
你在干吗?
What are you doing?
我要把这些带回去
I'm taking this back with us.
为什么?
Why?
因为这些可能很重要
Because they may be important.
重要?
Important?
等一下
I'm sorry.
你刚才不是跟我一起看了那段影片吗?
Weren't you just watching the same thing I was?
是的  John
Yes, John
我相信你一直在做的工作
and I believe the work you have been doing
十分重要 我愈加坚信这一点
is more important now than ever.
什么...工作?
What work?
按那个按键
Pushing the button.
那不是工作
That's not work.
那是
That's
一个笑话
a joke.
竹篮打水
Rats in a maze
一场空
with no cheese.
那是工作  John
It is work, John.
我们在被考验
We are being tested.
考验?
Tested?
按那个按键的原因...
The reason to do it, push the button,
不是因为在影片里他叫我们这么做
is not because we are told to do so in a film.
好吧
Oh, well.
那么原因是什么呢...
Well, then, what is the reason
Eko先生?
Mr. Eko?
我们做是因为我们相信自己注定要做
We do it because we believe we are meant to.
你不也是因为这才按按键的吗  John?
Isn't that the reason you pushed it, John?
我从来没有...
I was never
注定...
meant to
要去做任何事
do anything!
我那可悲的卑贱的生命里的每一秒钟
Every single second of my pathetic little life
都跟那个按键一样毫无意义
is as useless as that button!
你认为这很重要? 你认为这有必要?
You think it's important? You think it's necessary?
这些什么都不是  什么都不是
It's nothing. It's nothing.
这些毫无意义
It's meaningless.
你又凭什么告诉我这些?
And who are you to tell me that it's not?
这是815号航班  从23号门登机
That's flight 815 leaving from gate 23.
谢谢
Thank you.
你来这儿干嘛?
What are you doing here?
我要见你
I had to see you.
-听着  我父亲叫我别来... -我知道
-Look, your father said... -I know.
他不想让我和你说话
He doesn't want me talking to you
我知道你或许觉得我疯了
nd I know you probably think I'm crazy,
可我答应要给你带个口信
but I have a message for you and I promised to deliver it.
口信?
A message?
他说你是个好神父
He says you were a good priest.
谁说的?
Who says that?
Yemi
别拿我弟弟的名字...
Speaking about my brother
开玩笑
is not a joke,
当心你说的话
so you should be very careful what you say next.
当我在  另一个空间徘徊时 我见到了他
I saw him when I was between places.
他说你会来看我
He said that you would come and see me.
他说尽管你极力伪装
He said even though you were pretending,
你仍是个好人
you're a good man.
这是谁叫你说的?
Who put you up to this?
是你父亲吗?
Did your father tell you to do this?
他要我告诉你你们很快会见面的
He wants you to know he will see you soon.
他说尽管你对自己没信心
He said that even though you don't have faith in yourself
他对你却很有信心
he has faith in you.
你干吗这样对我?
Why are you doing this to me?
你想要什么? 你为什么这样做?
What do you want? Why are you doing this to me?
你们...
Is everything...
没事吧?
all right?
他相信你
He has faith in you.
总有一天  你会相信我的
One day you'll believe me.
这个十字架是我弟弟Yemi的
This cross was worn by my brother Yemi.
Yemi是个了不起的人
Yemi was a great man,
一个牧师
a priest
上帝的仆人
a man of God,
因为我背叛了他  他被枪杀了
and because I betrayed him, he was shot and died.
他被放在一架飞机上
He was placed on a plane
从尼日利亚的跑道起飞
which took off from an airstrip in Nigeria,
远在地球的另一边
half a world from here.
然后  我坐的飞机
Then the plane that I was on
在这个岛上坠毁了
crashed on this island.
不知何故  就在这儿
And somehow, here,
我又找到了我的弟弟
I found my brother again.
我在那架从尼日利亚起飞的飞机上发现了他
I found him in the same plane that took off from Nigeria,
就是现在我们上面的那架
in the same plane that lies above us now
掩盖住这个地方的飞机
that has concealed this place.
我从Yemi脖子上取下这个十字架
And I took this cross from around Yemi's neck
戴在自己脖子上
and put it back on mine.
就像
Just as it was
我第一次杀人的那天一样
on the day I first took another man's life.
所以我来问问你
So let me ask you,
你怎么能说这是没有意义呢?
how can you say this is meaningless?
我相信在那个舱子里的工作
I believe the work being done in the hatch
比什么都重要
is more important than anything.
如果你不继续按按键的话  John
If you will not continue to push the button, John...
我来按
I will.
我...
Can...
我能和她说说话么?
Can I talk to her?
当然
Sure.
是我  Hurley
It's Hurley.
Hugo
Hugo.
我很抱歉我忘了拿毯子
I'm sorry I forgot the blankets.
Libby?
Michael...
Michael...他很好
Michael. He's OK.
他挺过来了  Libby  没事了
He made it, Libby. It's OK.
没事了
It's all right.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====